comexbrokerage.com 2015-03-15

# COMEX Brokerage Limited - Premier Brokerage Firm

Our company understands the importance of personal information of every client. Cooperating with COMEX Brokerage Limited you can be sure in privacy of your personal information and in its protection by our employees. Our employees protect the collected by them information from unauthorized access. We use a variety of technologies to reduce the risk of liks of accounts and receiving personal information of our investors.

_Personal information_ includes such items as: 

  * Name and Last Name of the investor.
  * Locations.
  * Personal account of electronic currency.
  * Login and password.

Our company collects your personal information only with your consent and confidence in the security of your personal information on our program. T&C of our company explain, how your information is collected and used. Information which is collected when you visit this site.

Information that is automatically collected when you visiting our website,: 

  * Your Internet Provider.
  * Your location and country of residence.
  * Your browser and type of operating system.

This types of information are also the part of the personal information.

### Information Storage

Saving of information is only in our company or its equipment. Personal information is stored in accordance with the rules of storage and disposal, which are set for archive of our company. To receive your personal information, contact direct with our employees.

### Contact Information

If you have questions about the storage of personal information on this site, contact us via email support@comexbrokerage.com.
